Joker opened this weekend
record-breaking 93 million dollars yeah
I thought that wasn't fair because I've
been in plenty of movies people didn't
like and they didn't make 93 million but
I'm kidding not everyone had a problem
with the Joker it was obviously a hit
Joaquin Phoenix made an unannounced
appearance at a lot of screenings and
said hi to fans because that's what you
want
after a dark movie about mass murder a
surprise surprise in the dark meanwhile
Batman appear today chili cook-off and
Alhambra
I don't know if I want the star of the
movie sitting next to me while I'm
watching it you know I feel like I won't
give a proper yeah you'd be like ha ha
ha ha samples at Costco and you always
the ladies looking at about 200 to 300
other stars I prefer came in yeah and
very like terrifying
I think Joaquin Phoenix is a great actor
it's done great actor what I've seen on
talk shows and stuff not the best
conversationalist thank you
like there these guys are already
struggling with how disappointing this
movie is and they're like oh god I've
wasted a babysitter on this day oh I
agree he's such a weird dude like I feel
like are we sure that he wasn't just
working they're like are we sure he
might have been studying for another
part it doesn't do movies about two
years that he quirks it up big real
quirks ahoy he had to tone it down to
play the Joker
yeah also in the top 10 of the box
office it is also now clowns are getting
a real bad Raftis yeah alright I think
it's time for someone to make a fun
clown movie like remember when we were
fun
[Applause]
yeah it's such a fun run and now it I
know yeah I disagree
you're scared I'm saying Oh later guys
yeah let's go that was also a movie
whether it portrayed them in it but it
set the tone for killer Klowns
eye but now we need a fun one with us I
think clowns are actually murderers
right that's why you I don't remember
pounds are fun yeah they're all
murderers now I don't
clowns I'd like to say I remember when
you guys were fun
get it together clown you know the funny
thing is when he walked in he said
$15.00 for popcorn who's the real
criminal
[Music]
you